{
    "subject": "resource/Sakyo_Komatsu",
    "predicate": "ontology/genre",
    "object": "resource/Science_fiction",
    "human_readable": "Sakyo Komatsu's genre is Science fiction.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5583533644676208,
            "question": "What genre of writing is Sakyo Komatsu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.538557231426239,
            "question": "Are there any subgenres within Science fiction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5298168659210205,
            "question": "What makes a story fall into the Science fiction genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45343533158302307,
            "question": "What are some common themes found in Science fiction stories?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41642290353775024,
            "question": "Can you name a famous author who writes in the Science fiction genre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3742504119873047,
            "question": "Who are some popular authors of Science fiction novels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3374675512313843,
            "question": "How has Science fiction influenced popular culture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3133978545665741,
            "question": "What are some of the most iconic works of Science fiction literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2442249059677124,
            "question": "Can you give an example of a Science fiction movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17059464752674103,
            "question": "Why do people enjoy reading and watching Science fiction?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Sakyo Komatsu's genre is Science fiction.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8414_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give an example of a Science fiction movie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8414_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the most iconic works of Science fiction literature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8414_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Science fiction influenced popular culture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8414_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8414_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Sakyo Komatsu was a science fiction writer, supporting the statement that his genre is science fiction."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}